Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Labor Movement Serials WAG.345
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Labor unions and organizations, 1891-2012; 188.25 Linear Feet in 24 record cartons and 139 oversize flat boxes
  - Subseries I.I: Labor Coalitions and Organizations, 1905-2012; 25 Linear Feet in 3 record cartons, 1 manuscript box, and 19 oversize flat boxes
    - Honoring Fair Employment Practices Pioneers: 64th Annual Recognition Awards Brunch: Jewish Labor Committee - California/Western Region, Beverly Hills, CA, 1999 (Box 142, Folder 6)
    - Report: Jewish Labor Committee - N.Y. Workmen's Circle Division, New York, NY, 1943 (Box 142, Folder 7)
    - J.L.C. Bulletin: Jewish Labor Committee of Chicago, Chicago, IL, 1952 (Box 142, Folder 8)
    - Jobs with Justice: Jobs with Justice, Washington, DC, circa 1980s (Box 142, Folder 9)
    - PSL: L. T. Patterson, Cincinnati, OH, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 10)
    - L.A. Workers' Voice: L.A. Workers' Voice, Los Angeles, CA, 1994 (Box 142, Folder 11)
    - Picket Line: L.A.-Student-Worker Action Committee, Los Angeles, CA, 1971-1973 (Box 160, Folder 3)
    - Conference Report: Labor Action Coalition of New York, Ithaca, NY, 1979 (Box 142, Folder 12)
    - Labor Action: Labor Action Committee, 1954-1955, 1957, 1970-1973 (Box 151, Folder 6, Box 159, Folder 4)
    - Overtime: Labor Commission of the New America Movement, Chicago, IL, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 13)
    - Solidarity: Labor Committee of NY Students for a Democratic Society, New York, NY, 1969 (Box 151, Folder 7)
    - Hoe Hana: Labor Community Alliance, Honolulu, HI, 1974-1975 (Box 151, Folder 8)
    - New Jersey Labor Herald: Labor Herald Publishing Co., Newark, NJ, 1973-1975 (Box 151, Folder 9)
    - Labor Heritage Foundation News: Labor Heritage Foundation, Washington, DC, 1994-1995 (Box 142, Folder 14)
    - Labor and the Humanities: Labor Institute for Human Enrichment, Inc./National Endowment for the Humanities, Washington, DC, 1981 (Box 142, Folder 15)
    - Relay: Labor Institute of Public Affairs (AFL-CIO), Washington, DC, 1986 (Box 142, Folder 16)
    - Union Yes: Labor Institute of Public Affairs (AFL-CIO), 1993-1995 (Box 142, Folder 17)
    - Labor News: Labor News, Eureka, CA, 1905 (Box 151, Folder 10)
    - Labor News: Labor News, Worcester, MA, 1962 (Box 152, Folder 1)
    - Montana Labor News: Labor News, Butte, MT, 1947 (Box 160, Folder 4)
    - State Bulletin: Labor Non-Partisan League of New Jersey, Passaic, NJ / Trenton, NJ, 1938 (Box 142, Folder 18)
    - LODF Newsletter: Labor Organizers Defense Fund, New York, NY, 1975 (Box 142, Folder 19)
    - Labor Pains Newsletter: Labor Pains, Cambridge, MA, 1973 (Box 142, Folder 20)
    - Labor Party Press: Labor Party, Washington, DC, 1996-2002 (Box 152, Folder 2)
    - Worker/El Trabajador: Labor Party League, Montclair, CA, 1975 (Box 152, Folder 3)
    - LPON Newsletter: Labor Party Organizing Network, San Francisco, CA, 1993 (Box 142, Folder 21)
    - Newsletter: Labor Press Associates, Washington, DC, 1945 (Box 143, Folder 27)
    - Labor Reporter: Labor Press Unit, New York, NY, 1934 (Box 142, Folder 22)
    - Labor News for Working Families: Labor Project for Working Families, San Francisco, CA, 1994-1997 (Box 142, Folder 23)
    - Bulletin Labor Series: labor publications, New York, NY, 1972-1973 (Box 142, Folder 24)
    - Labor Publications Catalog: Labor Publications/Workers League, New York, NY, 1971 (Box 142, Folder 25)
    - Oklahoma Labor: Labor Publishing Co., Inc., Oklahoma City, OK, 1936 (Box 152, Folder 4)
    - Pennsylvania Labor Record: Labor Record, Inc., Philadelphia, Pa, 1943-1944 (Box 152, Folder 5-6, Box 38, Folder 3)
    - LRRC Labor Update: Labor Relations and Research Center, University of Massachusetts, Amherst, Amherst, MA, 1991 (Box 142, Folder 26)
    - Southern Labor in Wartime: Labor Research Association/International Publishers Co., Inc., 1942 (Box 142, Folder 27)
    - Labor Today: The Rank and File in Action: Labor Today Associates, Chicago, IL, 1973-1978 (Box 152, Folder 7)
    - Labor Vets Bulletin: Labor Veterans Group in AVC, Pittsburgh, PA, 1949 (Box 142, Folder 28)
    - Fact Against Fiction: Laborers' International Union of North America, Washington, DC, 1980 (Box 142, Folder 30)
    - Laborers' Benefits Review: Laborers' International Union of North America, Washington, DC, 1988 (Box 152, Folder 8)
    - Labor's Non-Partisan League National Bulletin: Labor's Non-Partisan League, Washington, DC, 1939 (Box 142, Folder 29)
    - Forward March of American Labor: League for Industrial Democracy, New York, NY, 1953 (Box 142, Folder 31)
    - League for Industrial Democracy News Bulletin: League for Industrial Democracy, New York, NY, 1942 (Box 142, Folder 32)
    - Local 721 Newsletter: Local 721, New York, NY, 1996-1999 (Box 142, Folder 33)
    - Local 966 Union News: Local 966, New York, NY, 1989 (Box 142, Folder 34)
    - Louisiana Labor/Neighbor Journal: Louisiana Labor and Neighbor Alliance, Baton Rouge, LA, 1991 (Box 142, Folder 35)
    - Mass. Rank & File: Mass. Rank & File, Northampton, MA, 1979 (Box 142, Folder 36)
    - Labor Press: Milwaukee County Labor Council (AFL-CIO), Milwaukee, WI, 1995 (Box 142, Folder 37)
    - Coal Field Defender: Miners News Service, Sharon, WV, 1979, 1981 (Box 152, Folder 9)
    - Minipress: Minifleet Association, Inc., New York, NY, 1984 (Box 152, Folder 10)
    - National Spotlight: Montgomery-Ward Organizing Committee, New York, NY, 1945 (Box 152, Folder 11)
    - Fun, Games, Money: Movement Labor New England Free Press, circa 1970s (Box 142, Folder 38)
    - Spark = La Chispa: N.Y.-N.J. United Workers Organization Electrical Committee, New York, NY, 1976-1977 (Box 152, Folder 12)
    - Bakery Workers Organize!: N.Y.-N.J. United Workers Organization Food Industry Committee, New York, NY, 1977 (Box 152, Folder 13)
    - Breaking Through/Workers Unite!: N.Y.-N.J. United Workers Organization Office Committee, New York, NY, 1976-1977 (Box 152, Folder 14)
    - Office Workers United: N.Y.-N.J. United Workers Organization Office Committee, New York, NY, 1974-1976 (Box 153, Folder 1)
    - Full Employment: Proceedings of the Conference on Full Employment CIO Political Action Committee: National Action Committee of the CIO, New York, NY, 1944 (Box 172, Folder 25)
    - NAAO Bulletin: National Association of Artists' Organizations, Washington, DC, 1988 (Box 173, Folder 6)
    - Histadru Foto News: National Committee for Labor Israel, Inc., New York, NY, 1967-1976 (Box 142, Folder 39)
    - Household Employment News: National Committee on Household Employment, Washington, DC, 1979 (Box 142, Folder 40)
    - FEPC Reference Manual: National Community Relations Advisory Council - Committee on Employment Discrimination, New York, NY, 1948 (Box 142, Folder 41)
    - Liguorian: National Council for Industrial Peace, Washington, DC, 1960 (Box 142, Folder 42)
    - Good Jobs for All: National Jobs for All Coalition, New York, NY, 2002 (Box 142, Folder 43)
    - Labor Campaign for Jailed Salvadoran Unionists: National Labor Committee in support of Democracy and Human Rights in El Salvador, New York, NY, 1984 (Box 142, Folder 44)
    - Newsletter: National Labor's Heritage Society, Silver Spring, MD, 1993 (Box 142, Folder 45)
    - Sweatshop Nation: National Mobilization Against Sweatshops (NMASS), New York, NY, 2000 (Box 153, Folder 2)
    - Your job or your Life?: National Mobilization Against Sweatshops (NMASS), New York, NY, 1997 (Box 142, Folder 46)
    - Unioncraft: National Organization of Industrial Trade Unions, New York, NY, 1970 (Box 142, Folder 47)
    - Where is the CIO going? By George Morris: New Century Publishers, 1949 (Box 142, Folder 48)
    - New England Labor News & Commentary: New England Labor News & Commentary, Inc., Nashua, NH, 1989 (Box 153, Folder 3)
    - New Hampshire Labor News: New Hampshire Federation of Labor, Manchester, NH, 1952 (Box 153, Folder 4)
    - IUC Action: New Jersey Industrial Union Council, AFL-CIO, Moorestown, NJ, 1996 (Box 142, Folder 49)
    - New Watch-Dog Committee: New Watch-dog Committee, Brooklyn, NY, 1975 (Box 142, Folder 50)
    - Annual Dinner Dance and Awards Ceremony: New York City Central Labor Council (AFL-CIO), New York, NY, 1999 (Box 142, Folder 51)
    - Labor Chronicle: New York City Central Labor Council (AFL-CIO), New York, NY, 1958, 1965, 1967-1969, 1972, 1974-1984 (Box 160, Folder 5-7)
    - Labor Council Alert: New York City Central Labor Council (AFL-CIO), New York, NY, 1993 (Box 142, Folder 52)
    - Trade Union Handbook: New York City Central Labor Council (AFL-CIO), New York, NY, 1975 (Box 142, Folder 53)
    - HSPAC News: New York City Central Labor Council (AFL-CIO) - Human Service Providers Advisory Committee, New York, NY, 1990 (Box 142, Folder 54)
    - CIO Community Services Newsletter: New York City CIO Council - Community Services Committee, New York, NY, 1954 (Box 142, Folder 55)
    - Fellow Worker: New York District Council (Industrial Workers of the World), New York, NY, 1920 (Box 153, Folder 5)
    - Disadvantaged Teacher: New York Labor Committee, New York, NY, 1970 (Box 142, Folder 56)
    - The Preamble of the Industrial Workers of the World: New York Labor News Company, New York, NY, 1915 (Box 142, Folder 57)
    - New York Labor Party: New York Labor Party, New York, NY, 1997-1998 (Box 142, Folder 58)
    - Labor Party Metro Active: New York Metro Chapter of the Labor Party, New York, NY, 1997-1998 (Box 142, Folder 59)
    - New York Credit Union News: New York State Credit Union League, Inc, New York, NY, 1936 (Box 142, Folder 60)
    - Combined Annual Reports of Officers of the New York State Federation of Labor: New York State Federation of Labor, Rochester, NY, 1946 (Box 172, Folder 28)
    - New York State Federation of Labor Bulletin: New York State Federation of Labor, New York, NY, 1936-1937 (Box 142, Folder 61)
    - Index: New York Trust Company, New York, NY, 1945 (Box 142, Folder 62)
    - League Bulletin: New York Women's Trade Union, New York, NY, 1940 (Box 142, Folder 63)
    - Strike Bulletin: Newspaper Guild of New York - World-Telegram & Sun Unit, New York, NY, 1950 (Box 142, Folder 64)
    - What is the non-partisan labor defense: Non-Partisan Labor Defense, New York, NY, circa 1940s (Box 142, Folder 65)
    - Labor & Environment News: NYC Labor & Environment Network, New York, NY, 1995 (Box 142, Folder 66)
    - Wildcat Report: NY-NJ Wildcat Action Group, New York, NY, 1969-1970 (Box 153, Folder 6)
    - Labor Report: NYS Assembly Labor Committee, 1977 (Box 142, Folder 67)
    - Employee Bulletin: NYS Department of Labor, Albany, NY, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 68)
    - O4O Newsletter: October 4th Organization, Philadelphia, PA, 1973-1974 (Box 142, Folder 69)
    - Single Spark: October 4th Organization, Philadelphia, PA, 1973 (Box 153, Folder 7)
    - Call/El Clarin: October League, 1979 (Box 153, Folder 8)
    - Owners at Work: Ohio Employee Ownership Center, Kent, OH, 2001 (Box 142, Folder 70)
    - Champ, Jr.: Ohio Valley District Council No. 2, Portsmouth, OH, 1950 (Box 142, Folder 71)
    - CIO News: Oil Workers International Union, Chicago, IL, 1944, 1946, 1950-1951 (Box 153, Folder 9, Box 159, Folder 5)
    - News from OCAW: Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union (AFL-CIO), Denver, CO, 1989 (Box 142, Folder 72)
    - Handbook for OCAW Women: Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers, Denver, CO, 1973 (Box 142, Folder 73)
    - Oil, Chemical and Atomic Union News: Official Publication of Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers Intl. Union--CIO: Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union, Denver, CO, 1983-1984 (Box 40, Folder 5)
      Researchers must use microfilm (Film R-7069)
    - Build a National Workers Organizations; Stand Up Fight Together: Organizing Committee for a National Workers Organization, Milwaukee, WI, 1977 (Box 142, Folder 74)
    - Organizer: National Newsletter of the Organizing Committee for a National Workers Organization: Organizing Committee for a National Workers Organization, Milwaukee, WI, 1977-1978 (Box 153, Folder 10)
    - Our Times: Our Times Cooperative, Toronto, Canada, 1982 (Box 153, Folder 11)
    - Outlaw: Outlaw Collective, St. Louis, Mo., 1971 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - PACEsetter: PACE International Union, Nashville, TN, 1999-2000 (Box 153, Folder 13-14)
    - New York Workers' News and Perspective: Pasternack, A., Brooklyn, NY, 1976-1978 (Box 153, Folder 15)
    - Bulletin of the People's Council of America: People's Council of America, New York, NY, 1917 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - People's Voice: People's Voice, Detroit, MI, 1974-1975 (Box 153, Folder 16)
    - People's Voice: People's Voice, Maywood, IL, 1973 (Box 154, Folder 1)
    - People's Voice: People's Voice, Inc., Somerville, MA, 1973-1977 (Box 154, Folder 2)
    - Philadelphia Free Press: Philadelphia Free Press, Philadelphia, PA, 1973 (Box 154, Folder 3)
    - Trade Union Question: Philadelphia Organizing Committee, Philadelphia, PA, 1977 (Box 142, Folder 75)
    - Workers' Councils and the Economics of a Self-Managed Society: Philadelphia Solidarity, Philadelphia, PA, 1974 (Box 142, Folder 76)
    - Organizer: Philadelphia Workers' Organizing Committee, Philadelphia, Pa, 1975-1981, 1987-1988 (Box 148, Folder 1-5)
    - Turn It Around!: Philadelphia Workers' Organizing Committee, Philadelphia, Pa, 1971 (Box 173, Folder 15)
    - Philly Facts: Philadelphia-TWU Local 235, Philadelphia, Pa, 1945 (Box 154, Folder 4)
    - Work Ethics: Newsletter of the Plant Closures Project: Plant Closures Project, Oakland, CA, 1984 (Box 142, Folder 77)
    - Sargent Bulletin # 89: Porter Sargent, Boston, MA, 1940 (Box 142, Folder 78)
    - Progressive Voice: Progressive Group in Workers Alliance, New York, NY, 1938 (Box 142, Folder 79)
    - Pueblo: Pueblo, San Juan, Puerto Rico, 1970 (Box 154, Folder 5)
    - Rank and Filer: Rank & Filer, New York, NY, 1970 (Box 154, Folder 6)
    - New York Painter and Decorator: Rank and File Inter-Club Conference, New York, NY, 1936-1937 (Box 154, Folder 7)
    - Working for a Living: Rational Island Publishers, Seattle, WA, 1977 (Box 142, Folder 80)
    - TWU Free Press: Reick Committee in the Interest of Local 235, 1960 (Box 142, Folder 81)
    - Labor's Champion: Organ of the Central Committee of the Revolutionary Political Organization (Marxist-Leninist) USA: Revolutionary Political Organization, New Orleans, La, 1985-1991 (Box 147, Folder 1-6)
    - Workers' History Calendar: Revolutionary Union, Chicago, IL, 1973-1975 (Box 142, Folder 82)
    - Movin' On = Moviéndo se: Revolutionary Workers Congress, Detroit, MI, 1975 (Box 154, Folder 8)
    - Labor Challenge: Revolutionary Workers Party, Toronto, Canada, 1946, 1951-1952 (Box 52, Folder 20)
    - Worker: Rhode Island Workers Association, Providence, RI, 1975 (Box 142, Folder 83)
    - R.I.W.A. Organizing Center Reports/Assorted reports: Rhode Island Workers Association Organizing Center, Providence, RI, 1976 (Box 142, Folder 84)
    - People Get Ready: Richmond Worker's Committee, Richmond, CA, 1970 (Box 154, Folder 10)
    - Row 'A' Review: Row 'A' Review Campaign Committee, 1944 (Box 154, Folder 11)
    - Local 6 Liberator: Save The Union Committee, New York, NY, 1951 (Box 154, Folder 12)
    - Seattle Semi: Seattle Semi, Seattle, WA, 1976 (Box 142, Folder 85)
    - Industrial & Allied Update: Service Employees International Union (SEIU) - Industrial & Allied Division (AFL-CIO, CLC), Washington, DC, 1988-1992 (Box 142, Folder 86)
    - Meatballs: SHAP-affiliated, 2002 (Box 142, Folder 87)
    - Solidarity Organizing Committee/Comite Organizador Solidaridad: Solidarity Organizing Committee, Brooklyn, NY, 1992-1994 (Box 143, Folder 1)
    - Union Labor News: South Central Federation of Labor, Madison, WI, 1993 (Box 154, Folder 13)
    - Fair Measure: Newsletter of Southerners for Economic Justice: Southerners for Economic Justice, Greenville, SC, 1978, 1982-1984 (Box 154, Folder 14)
    - The Spark: Spark, Detroit, MI, 1989 (Box 143, Folder 2)
    - Spark Western Voice for Revolution = Chispa de Revolution: SPARK-CHISPA, San Francisco, CA, 1966 (Box 154, Folder 15)
    - Speaking Out: Speaking Out, Detroit, MI, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 3)
    - Illinois Tradesman: Springfield Federation of Labor, Springfield, IL, 1954 (Box 52, Folder 19)
    - Minnesota Union Advocate: St. Paul Trades & Labor Assembly, St. Paul, MN, 1997 (Box 154, Folder 17)
    - Union Advocate: St. Paul Trades & Labor Assembly, St. Paul, MN, 1997 (Box 154, Folder 9)
    - Strike!: STRIKE! Publishing Association, 1981-1986 (Box 155, Folder 1-2)
    - Open City: Strike-New York, Bronx, NY, 1970 (Box 154, Folder 16)
    - Brockwood Review: Students and Faculty of Brockwood, Katonah, NY, 1929 (Box 155, Folder 3)
    - Union Voice: Suffolk County Head Start Union Workers, Amityville, NY, 1987 (Box 143, Folder 4)
    - People Get Ready: Sunbeam Workers, Chicago, IL, circa 1970s (Box 172, Folder 29)
    - El Obrero rebelde: Synthesis Publications, San Francisco, CA, 1979 (Box 155, Folder 4)
    - Outlaw Times: The Outlaw, Dallas, TX, 1971 (Box 155, Folder 5)
    - Red Album: Toiler, Cleveland, OH, 1921 (Box 143, Folder 5)
    - Toledo Consumers' League: Toledo Consumers' League, Toledo, OH, 1930, 1933 (Box 143, Folder 6)
    - Working Press: Tompkins/Cortland Labor Coalition (TCLC), Ithaca, NY, 1987-1994 (Box 155, Folder 6-7)
    - Discussion Bulletin: Trade Union Commission, 1976 (Box 172, Folder 22)
    - Rank and File Federationist/A.F. of L. Rank and File Federationist: Trade Union Committee for Unemployment Insurance Relief - A.F. of L. Trade Union Committee, New York, NY, 1933-1935 (Box 159, Folder 2)
    - New York Teamster: Trade Union Courier, New York, NY, 1976 (Box 155, Folder 8)
    - Trade Union Courier: Trade Union Courier, New York, NY, 1948, 1978, 1997-2003 (Box 156, Folder 19-20, Box 157, Folder 1-3, Box 158, Folder 1-4)
    - Union Courier: Trade Union Courier Publishing Corp., New York, NY, 1950 (Box 159, Folder 3)
    - Labor Herald Library: Trade Union Educational League, Chicago, IL, circa 1920s (Box 143, Folder 7-8)
    - Vanguard: Trade Union Leadership Council, Inc., Detroit, MI, 1963 (Box 155, Folder 9)
    - Demands for Unemployment Insurance Made upon the United States Congress: Trade Union Unity League, 1931 (Box 172, Folder 26)
    - Red International of Labour Unions: Trade Union Unity League of America, New York, NY, circa 1930 (Box 143, Folder 9)
    - Strike Back: Trenton Area United Workers, Trenton, NJ, 1971 (Box 146, Folder 5)
    - Boletin Mensual: Union General de Trabajadores, 1950-1951 (Box 155, Folder 10)
    - Union Label Trades News and Directory: Union Label Trades Department of the State of New York/Union Label League & Central Body Label Committees of the State of New York, New York, NY, 1951 (Box 155, Folder 11)
    - Racine Labor: Union Labor Publishing Company Inc., Racine, WI, 1992-1995 (Box 155, Folder 12)
    - Unionist: Unionist, Austin, MN, 1986 (Box 156, Folder 2)
    - Cornell Union Scribbler: United Auto Workers - Local 188 - Students of Professor Harry Kelber, Ithaca, NY, 1966 (Box 143, Folder 10)
    - Build the Nationwide Unemployed League: United Front Committee to Build the Nationwide Unemployed League, New York, NY, 1975 (Box 156, Folder 3)
    - U.I.W. 424 News: United Industry Workers 425, Bohemia, NY, 1989 (Box 143, Folder 11)
    - Review and Outlook: United Labor-Management Press, New York, NY, 1961 (Box 143, Folder 12)
    - Songs for May Day: United May Day Committee, New York, NY, 1946 (Box 159, Folder 6)
    - Newsletter: United MayDay Committee, 1975 (Box 143, Folder 13)
    - District 50 News: United Mine Workers of America, Washington, DC, 1946 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Chemical Worker: United Mine Workers of America - District 50, Local #12165, Drug, Chemical and Cosmetic Division, 1940 (Box 143, Folder 14)
    - Coal Miners and the Economy: A UMWA Research Report: United Mine Workers of America - Research Department, Washington, DC, 1974 (Box 143, Folder 15)
    - Memo: United Office and Professional Workers of America - Local 16, New York, NY, 1943 (Box 156, Folder 4)
    - Packinghouse Workers Champion: United Packinghouse Workers of America - District One, Chicago, IL, 1944 (Box 156, Folder 5)
    - Public Record: United Public Workers of America, New York, NY, 1950, 1952 (Box 156, Folder 6, Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Our Newspaper: United Workers Association, 1976 (Box 143, Folder 16)
    - Newark Airport Cab Driver's Bulletin: Unity and Struggle, Newark, NJ, 1974 (Box 156, Folder 7)
    - University of Illinois bulletin: University of Illinois, Urbana, IL, 1961, 1967 (Box 143, Folder 17)
    - CONET: University of Minnesota, 1991 (Box 143, Folder 18)
    - Trenton Rank & File: UTF, Trenton, NJ, 1972 (Box 156, Folder 8)
    - Vermont Labor Reporter: Vermont Labor Council, AFL-CIO, Bellows Falls, VT, 1968, 1975 (Box 156, Folder 9)
    - Bulletin: Washington State Nursing Home Resident Council, Seattle, WA, 1982-1983 (Box 172, Folder 23)
    - The NATCA Voice: The Great Lakes Regional NATCA Newsletter: West End Press, Chicago, IL, 1995 (Box 172, Folder 21)
    - West Virginia Mine Workers Campaign Bulletin: West Virginia Mine Workers, Charleston, WV, 1931 (Box 156, Folder 10)
    - Westchester 60 Plus: Westchester County Office for the Aging, White Plains, NY, 1992 (Box 156, Folder 11)
    - What's Left: Western Massachusetts Labor/Community Support Network, Northampton, MA, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 19)
    - Abestos Update: White Lung Asbestos Information Center, New York, NY, 1995-1998 (Box 143, Folder 20)
    - Wildfire: Wildfire, Chicago, IL, 1975-1976 (Box 156, Folder 12)
    - Philadelphia Worker: Worker, Philadelphia, Pa, 1975 (Box 156, Folder 13)
    - Rochester Worker: Worker, Rochester, NY, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Subways are for sitting: Worker, circa 1960s (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - A Call to Organize: Worker's Action Comm., Elmhurst, IL, 1970 (Box 143, Folder 21)
    - Workers Action/Obreros en Acción: Workers Action Movement, Chicago, IL, 1974 (Box 156, Folder 14)
    - NYU Workers' Voice: Workers at New York University, New York, NY, 1972 (Box 172, Folder 19)
    - Workers Defense Bulletin: Workers Defense League, New York, NY, 1947-1949 (Box 143, Folder 22)
    - Workers Defense League - Anniversary Journal: Workers Defense League, New York, NY, 1972, 1981, 1983 (Box 143, Folder 23)
    - Last-Minute News: Workers Defense League - National Office, New York, NY, circa 1940 (Box 143, Folder 24)
    - Workers Democracy: Workers' Democracy Network, Trenton, NJ, 2003 (Box 156, Folder 16)
    - New World: Workers Press, New York, N.Y., 2008-2009 (Box 156, Folder 15)
    - Democratizing the Workplace - Ideas Examples and Suggestions on Democratizing the Workplace from Job Enrichment to Worker Control: Workers' Self-Management Group, AFSC, Cambridge, MA, circa 1970 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Working Families News: Working Families, Brooklyn, NY, 2000 (Box 143, Folder 25)
    - Southerner: Dalton, GA, 1955 (Box 156, Folder 17)
  - Subseries I.J: Public Employees, 1921-2005; 11 Linear Feet in 2 record cartons and 8 oversize flat boxes